{"data":[{"question":"Moira lives ____ Toronto.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"Columbus discovered America _____ 1492.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\non\/off campus\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"The controller for Acme Corp. testified _____ the Senate hearing today.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"he cat sat____the mat.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"The concert is ____ 24 September.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"Mr. Thompson isn't here right now. He's _____ the bank.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"Julia goes to her fitness class _____ Tuesdays.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"I went to a party____New Year's Eve.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"There is someone _____ the door.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- In the north\/south...of somewhere","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"This is the best cake _____ the world.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"}]}